xdesktopwallpapers.com 2019-05-07

# Privacy Policy

**Last Updated On – June 1st, 2014**

**xDesktopWallpapers.com** knows that you care how information about you is used and shared on internet, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This page describes our privacy policy. For any question on the Privacy Notice please [Contact Us](http://xdesktopwallpapers.com/wp-content/contact/ "Contact Us for Feedback & Suggestions").

### What Personal Information About Me Does xDesktopWallpapers.com Gather?

**_Information You Provided:_**

We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, providing our services, and communicating with you.

**_Information Automatically Logged:_**

We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with our site.

For example, like many other Web sites, we use “cookies,” Examples of the information we collect and analyze include the Internet protocol (IP), computer and connection information such as browser type and version, OS (Operating System), and platform; the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL) click stream to, through, and from our Web site, including date and time.

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement, and gather broad demographic information to configure the website to provide the best services to you.

### Cookies and Information Collected by Third Parties?

Cookies are very small piece of text files placed on your hard disk by a computer server.

It serves as your like an identification card and its is uniquely yours.

Cookies tell us that you returned to a specific Web page on our Site, and help us track your preferences and transactional habits and help us to “remember” who you are.

Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses, Trojans to your computer.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies.

Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies by default, but you can easily modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you want.

If you reject a cookie you may still use our Site but your use will be limited in some areas of our Web-Site.

Our Site may include third-party advertising and links to other websites. The information in the cookies is specifically handled by external advertising agencies who serve the ads that you see on the website.

### What about Children’s Privacy?

Children under the age of 14 are not allowed to use the Site.

We does not knowingly collect Personal Information about children under the age of 14 or allow them to use the Site.

If We learns that a child under the age of 14 is using the Site, **xDesktopWallpapers.com** will close the child’s account and delete all information collected about the child.

But we may choose to retain the child’s e-mail address as a means to prevent the child from re-registering with xDesktopWallpapers.com.

### External Links:

Our site contains links to other sites.

We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any websites whose links are provided on this website or those which link to us.

We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information.

This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

### Send Wallpapers to the Other:

When you use ‘Email The Wallpaper’ feature to send wallpapers to your friends, the email address of the sender and recipient is recorded by us.

This is done to protect all internet users’ interest in the process of preventing abuse & curbing spam.

These email addresses are not used in any mailing lists or in any form of spam.

### Contacting the Web Master:

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please contact the Webmaster [Here](http://xdesktopwallpapers.com/wp-content/contact/ "Contact Us for Feedback & Suggestions").

__02 Jun 2014 __1
